Register of the Survey of Race Relations records
Hoover Institution Archives
Survey of Race Relations records
1905-1934
61003
Hoover Institution Archives
38 manuscript boxes (15.2 linear feet)
An anthropological investigative project sponsored by various private organizations, the Survey of Race Relations records include a report, correspondence, interview transcripts, questionnaires, and printed matter relating to the social and economic status of Chinese, Japanese, other Asian, Mexican, and other minority residents of the Pacific Coast of the United States and Canada, and to race relations on the Pacific Coast.
Survey of Race Relations.
Access
Collection is open for research. Collection stored off site; a minimum of two days notice is required for use. Boxes may be requested through Stanford's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu. Digital copies of materials are available online through the Stanford Digital Repository; links to individual box contents can be found throughout the finding aid at the relevant box entry.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1961.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Alternate Forms Available
Digital copies of materials are available online through the Stanford Digital Repository; links to box contents can be found throughout the finding aid.
Historical Note
In the early 1920s, a group of scholars set out to make an investigation of economic, religious, educational, civic, biological, and social conditions among Chinese, Japanese, and other non-European residents of the Pacific Coast of the United States and Canada. Extension of the study into northern Mexico and Hawaii was contemplated as well. The Survey had its administrative and research headquarters at Stanford University under the chairmanship of President Ray Lyman Wilbur and was under the research directorship first of Stanford professor Eliot G. Mears and subsequently of the Chicago sociologist, Robert E. Park. The Survey received important financial support and collaboration from the Institute of Social and Religious Research.
In the words of Mears, Executive Secretary, "The Survey seeks to impose no program, advocates no specific policy, and champions no special interest. It aims to find the facts, and all the facts, and plans to make them accessible to the public." The findings were to be published in a series of volumes edited by Dr. Park.
After only one publication ("Tentative Findings of the Survey of Race Relations," edited by Mears), the Survey ran out of money, and research was discontinued.
Later, Mears wrote a book based on the work of the Survey entitled, Resident Orientals on the American Pacific Coast: Their Legal and Economic Status, 1928.
Scope and Content of Collection
Completed life-history questionnaires comprise the greatest bulk and are the "raw data" of the collection. In addition, there are numerous open-ended personal reflections, financial records, conference reports, meeting notes, bibliographies, printed materials and miscellaneous other findings of the Survey. The original manuscript of Mears' book Resident Orientals on the American Pacific Coast: Their Legal and Economic Status is also included in the collection.
The following items are missing documents from the original accession; the items would have been a part of the Minor Documents series: 1 (items #53-54 out of the 102 interviews in that folder 1), 4-9, 11, 13-17, 19-21, 23, 25-30, 32-36, 39, 49-50, 67-74, 81, 83, 85, 89-90, 92, 94-100, 102-105, 107-118, 120-122, 125-130, 132-145, 147-148, 150-151, 153-161, 163, 166-172, 174-175, 178, 184-186, 195-249, 257-260, 263, 268, 274, 294-312.
The classification titles and codes of the documents as established by the Survey of Race Relations can be found below under File Plan.
File Plan
Survey of Race Relations records, 1924-1927
File Plan: Classification Titles
Classification titles and codes of the documents as established by the Survey of Race Relations
I. Americanization: Am
a) Second generation (2nd Gen
b) Family problems (F. P.
c) Accommodation (Accom.
d) Vocational problems (Voc.
e) Education (Ed.
f) Naturalization (Nat.
II. Communities: Com.
a) Organization of (Org.
b) Activities
c) Standards of living (S. L.
III. Competition and Land: Comp.
a) Agriculture (Agric.
b) Land ownership (Land Own.
c) Labor
d) Cropping contract (C. C.
e) Business (Bus.
f) Employment contract (Employ. C.
IV. Good-Will: G. W.
a) Religious activities (Relig.
b) Friendship
V. Heritages: Her.
a) Oriental/Asiatic (O.
b) Chinese (C.
c) Japanese (J.
d) East Indian (E. I.
e) Filipino (F.
f) Mexican (M.
g) Korean (K.
h) Hindu (H.
i) Tongs
VI. Intermarriage: Int.
a) Eurasian child
VII. Investigations: Inv.
a) Statistics (Stat.
b) Legislation (Legis.
c) Historical (Hist.
VIII. Life Histories: L. H.
a) Oriental/Asiatic (O.
b) Chinese (C.
c) Japanese (J.
d) East Indian (E. I.
e) Filipino (F.
f) Mexican (M.
g) Korean (K.
h) Hindu (H.
i) Tongs
IX. Population: Pop.
a) Immigration (Im.
b) Vital statistics
c) Distribution
d) Movement (Mvt.
X. Race Consciousness: R. C.
a) Conflict
b) Prejudice (Prej.
c) Discrimination
d) Public opinion (Pub. Op.
e) Political tension (P. T.
XI. Racial Traits: R. T.
a) Oriental/Asiatic (O.
b) Chinese (C.
c) Japanese (J.
d) East Indian (E. I.
e) Filipino (F.
f) Mexican (M.
g) Korean (K.
h) Hindu (H.
i) Tongs
j) American (A.
XII. Social Disorganization: S. D.
a) Vice and crime (V. C.
b) Poverty
c) Disease
d) Prostitution (Prost.
e) Gambling
f) Delinquency
XIII. Other
a) Organization (Organiz.
b) Illegal entry (Ill. Entry
c) Industry (Ind.
Asian Americans.; Asians--Canada.; Chinese Americans.; Japanese Americans.; Mexican Americans.; Minorities--Canada.; Minorities--United States.; Canada--Race relations.; United States--Race relations.
- Office File, 1914-1928 (Boxes 1-23)
  Access
  Collection stored off site; a minimum of two days notice is required for use. Boxes may be requested through Stanford's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu. Digital copies of materials are available online through the Stanford Digital Repository; links to individual box contents can be found throughout the finding aid at the relevant box entry.
  Scope and Contents note
  Addresses, bibliographies, charts, clippings and other printed matter, conference file, correspondence, financial records, interviews, lists, memoranda, minutes of meetings, notes, outlines, programs, projects, proposals, questionnaires, remarks, reports, speeches, statements, studies, tables and statistical data, work plans, and writings relating to operations of the Survey of Race Relations, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Digital copy of Box 1
  - General (Box-folder 1: 1-3)
    Includes fragments and some unidentified materials.
  - Addresses by J. Merle Davis, K. J. Saunders, and Frank A. Vanderlip (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Bibliographies (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Charts, including on the percentage of increase and distribution in the total Chinese and Japanese population on the Pacific Coast and in the United States in general (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Clippings and other printed matter
    - General (Box-folder 1: 7-9)
    - Digital copy of Box 2
    - General (Box-folder 2: 1)
    - 1915-1918 (Box-folder 2: 2)
    - 1919-1922 (Box-folder 2: 3)
    - Digital copy of Box 3
    - 1923 - 1924 February (Box-folder 3: 1)
    - 1924
      - March-July (Box-folder 3: 2)
      - August-November (Box-folder 3: 3)
    - 1925
      - January-March (Box-folder 3: 4)
      - May-September (Box-folder 3: 5)
      - Digital copy of Box 4
      - October–December (Box-folder 4: 1)
    - 1926-1927 (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - Conference file
    Includes correspondence, proceedings, and related materials.
    - Ninth Conference on the California-Japanese problem, San Francisco, California, 1922 October 11 (Box-folder 4: 3)
    - Group Conference for Organization and Cooperation in Pacific Coast Oriental Survey, San Francisco, California, 1923 June 13 (Box-folder 4: 4)
    - Group Conference for Organization and Cooperation in Pacific Coast Oriental Survey, Portland, Oregon, 1923 June 16 (Box-folder 4: 5)
      Includes letter from J. Merle Davis.
    - Conference of the Committee on Japanese Relations, Chamber of Commerce of San Francisco, San Francisco, California, 1923 July 27 (Box-folder 4: 6)
    - Findings Conference of the Survey of Race Relations, Stanford University, Stanford, California, 1925 March 21-26
      - General (Box-folder 4: 7-13)
      - Digital copy of Box 5
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 5: 1-4)
      - Typescript (Box-folder 5: 5-8)
        Includes some holograph.
    - Proposed Pan-Pacific Conference on a Christian Program for the Pacific Area, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1925 July 1-15
      - General (Box-folder 5: 9)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 5: 10)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 5: 11)
  - Correspondence
    Includes related materials.
    - General
      - General
        - General (Box-folder 5: 12-13)
        - Digital copy of Box 6
        - General (Box-folder 6: 1-3)
          Includes correspondence relating to requests for materials.
        - With community leaders (Box-folder 6: 4)
        - With survey leaders (Box-folder 6: 5)
      - Alphabetical
        - General (Box-folder 6: 6)
        - Bogardus, Emory S., 1924-1925 (Box-folder 6: 7)
        - Bowen, Trevor, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 6: 8)
        - California Development Association, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 6: 9)
        - California Farm Bureau Federation, 1923 (Box-folder 6: 10)
        - California State Church Federation, 1924 (Box-folder 6: 11)
        - Davis, J. Merle
          - 1921-1923 (Box-folder 6: 12)
          - Digital copy of Box 7
          - 1924-1926 (Box-folder 7: 1-2)
        - Fisher, Galen M., 1922-1927 (Box-folder 7: 3-5)
        - Gleason, George, 1922-1925 (Box-folder 7: 6-7)
        - Digital copy of Box 8
        - Gulick, Sidney, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 8: 1)
        - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 8: 2-3)
        - Jordan, David Starr, 1923-1925 (Box-folder 8: 4)
        - Los Angeles Chamber of Commerce, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 8: 5)
        - MacCaughey, Vaughan
          - 1923 - 1924 April (Box-folder 8: 6-8)
          - Digital copy of Box 9
          - 1924 May – 1925 (Box-folder 9: 1-2)
        - McClatchy, V. S., 1922-1925 (Box-folder 9: 3)
        - McKenzie, R. D., 1924-1925 (Box-folder 9: 4)
        - Mears, Eliot G.
          - 1924 (Box-folder 9: 5)
          - Digital copy of Box 10
          - 1925
            - January-March (Box-folder 10: 1)
            - April-June (Box-folder 10: 2)
            - July-December (Box-folder 10: 3)
          - Digital copy of Box 11
          - 1926-1928 (Box-folder 11: 1-2)
        - Mott, John R., 1922-1924 (Box-folder 11: 3)
        - Native Sons of the Golden West, 1923 (Box-folder 11: 4)
        - Nelson, John, 1923-1925 (Box-folder 11: 5)
        - Park, Robert E., 1923-1926 (Box-folder 11: 6-8)
        - Parsons, Philip A., 1924-1925 (Box-folder 11: 9)
        - Raushenbush, Winifred, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 11: 10)
        - Rosecrans, W. S., 1924 (Box-folder 11: 11)
        - Saunders, K. J., 1924 (Box-folder 11: 12)
        - Treat, Katharine W., 1927 (Box-folder 11: 13)
        - Wilbur, Ray Lyman
          - 1923-1924 (Box-folder 11: 14)
          - Digital copy of Box 12
          - 1925-1927 (Box-folder 12: 1)
        - Wilkie, Charles D., 1924-1925 (Box-folder 12: 2)
        - Zimmerman, J. F., 1923-1924 (Box-folder 12: 3)
      - Chronological, 1924-1927 (Box-folder 12: 4)
      - Topical
        - East-Indians – U.S., 1923-1924 (Box-folder 12: 5)
        - Fishing – Pacific Coast (U.S.), 1927 (Box-folder 12: 6)
        - Japanese-Americans – Education – U.S., 1924 (Box-folder 12: 7)
        - Land tenure – Pacific Coast (U.S), 1925-1927 (Box-folder 12: 8)
        - Manufacturing – Pacific Coast (U.S.), 1927 (Box-folder 12: 9)
        - Miners – Pacific Coast (U.S.), 1927 (Box-folder 12: 10)
        - Minorities – Employment – Pacific Coast (U.S.), 1927 (Box-folder 12: 11)
        - Pacific Coast (U.S.) – Commerce, 1924-1927 (Box-folder 12: 12)
        - Professions – Pacific Coast (U.S.), 1927 (Box-folder 12: 13)
    - Digital copy of Box 13
    - British Columbia (Canada), 1923-1924 (Box-folder 13: 1-2)
    - California, Northern
      - General, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 13: 3-4)
      - Cities
        - Berkeley, 1924 (Box-folder 13: 5)
        - Fresno, 1924 (Box-folder 13: 6)
        - Livingston, 1924 (Box-folder 13: 7)
        - Oakland, 1924 (Box-folder 13: 8)
        - Palo Alto, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 13: 9)
        - San Francisco, 1924 (Box-folder 13: 10)
        - San Jose, 1924 (Box-folder 13: 11)
        - Saratoga, 1924 (Box-folder 13: 12)
        - Stockton, 1924 (Box-folder 13: 13)
    - California, Southern
      - General, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 13: 14)
      - Cities
        - Los Angeles, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 13: 15)
        - Pasadena, 1924 (Box-folder 13: 16)
        - Digital copy of Box 14
        - San Diego, 1924 (Box-folder 14: 1)
      - Counties
        - Imperial, 1924 (Box-folder 14: 2)
        - Orange, 1924 (Box-folder 14: 3)
        - Riverside, 1924 (Box-folder 14: 4)
        - San Bernadino, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 14: 5)
        - Santa Barbara, 1924 (Box-folder 14: 6)
        - Ventura, 1924 (Box-folder 14: 7)
    - Oregon, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 14: 8-9)
    - Washington, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 14: 10-11)
    - Miscellany, 1924-1928 (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - Digital copy of Box 15
  - Financial records (Box-folder 15: 1-13)
  - Interviews
    - General
      - General (Box-folder 15: 14)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 15: 15)
    - Regional
      - British Columbia (Box-folder 15: 16)
      - California (Box-folder 15: 17)
  - Lists
    - General (Box-folder 15: 18-19)
      Includes lists of major and minor documents.
    - Personnel and topical (Box-folder 15: 20)
    - Regional (Box-folder 15: 21)
  - Memoranda
    - General (Box-folder 15: 22)
    - Los Angeles (Calif.) (Box-folder 15: 23)
  - Digital copy of Box 16
  - Minutes of meetings (Box 16)
    - General (Box-folder 16: 1-2)
    - British Columbia (Canada) (Box-folder 16: 3)
    - California, Northern (Box-folder 16: 4-6)
    - California, Southern
      - General (Box-folder 16: 7-8)
        Includes meetings of the missionaries from the Philippines, Korea, and China living in Southern California.
      - Cities, Los Angeles (Calif.) (Box-folder 16: 9)
      - Counties
        - Orange (Box-folder 16: 10)
        - San Diego (Box-folder 16: 11)
        - Santa Barbara (Box-folder 16: 12)
        - Ventura (Box-folder 16: 13)
    - Pacific Coast (Box-folder 16: 14)
    - Pacific Coast and Hawaii (Box-folder 16: 15)
    - Washington (Box-folder 16: 16-17)
  - Notes
    - Undated (Box-folder 16: 18)
      Includes notes from a lecture by David Starr Jordan.
    - 1923 (Box-folder 16: 19)
      Including of John R. Mott's talk at the Spokane Association, Spokane, Washington.
  - Programs (Box-folder 16: 20)
  - Projects
    - General (Box-folder 16: 21-22)
    - California, Northern (Box-folder 16: 23)
    - California, Southern (Box-folder 16: 24)
    - Pacific Coast (Box-folder 16: 25)
    - Washington (Box-folder 16: 26)
  - Proposals (Box-folder 16: 27)
    Including by Robert E. Park.
  - Digital copy of Box 17
  - Questionnaires
    - General
      - General
        - General
          - General (Box-folder 17: 1)
          - Chinese – Pacific Coast (U.S.) and Canada (Box-folder 17: 2)
          - Hindus – Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 17: 3)
          - Japanese – Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 17: 4)
          - Orientals – Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 17: 5)
        - Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 17: 6)
        - San Jose (Calif.) (Box-folder 17: 7-8)
      - Agriculture – United States (Box-folder 17: 9)
      - Intermarriage – Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 17: 10)
      - Labor – United States (Box-folder 17: 11)
    - Replies (Box-folder 17: 12)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Remarks (Box-folder 17: 14)
    Including by Robert E. Park, Regional Council, Vancouver, Canada, 1923 September 14 and by Albert H. Eliot on real property – California – foreign ownership.
  - Reports
    - General (Box-folder 17: 15-17)
      Includes report on deportations to Toledo, Oregon.
    - British Columbia and Canada (Box-folder 17: 18-20)
    - California (Box-folder 17: 21)
    - California, Northern
      - General
        - Fresno (Box-folder 17: 22)
        - Sacramento and Turlock (Box-folder 17: 23)
        - San Jose (Box-folder 17: 24)
      - Digital copy of Box 18
      - Butte county (Box-folder 18: 1)
      - Sonoma county (Box-folder 18: 2)
    - California, Southern
      - General
        - General (Box-folder 18: 3)
        - Los Angeles (Box-folder 18: 4)
      - Imperial county (Box-folder 18: 5)
      - Orange county (Box-folder 18: 6)
      - Riverside county (Box-folder 18: 7)
      - San Bernadino county (Box-folder 18: 8)
      - San Diego county (Box-folder 18: 9)
      - Ventura county (Box-folder 18: 10)
    - Hawaii (Box-folder 18: 11)
    - Northwest, Pacific (Pacific Northwest) (Box-folder 18: 12)
    - Oregon (Box-folder 18: 13)
    - Pacific Coast (Box-folder 18: 14)
    - Washington (Box-folder 18: 15)
  - Speeches (Box-folder 18: 16)
  - Statements (Box-folder 18: 17)
    Including by V. S. McClatchy and John R. Mott.
  - Studies (Box-folder 18: 18-20)
  - Subject file
    Correspondence and other related materials.
    - Agriculture – Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 18: 21-22)
    - Digital copy of Box 19
    - Agriculture – Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 19: 1-3)
    - Chinese – Pacific Coast (U.S.) and Canada (Box-folder 19: 4-6)
    - Dairy workers – Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 19: 7)
    - Filipinos – Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 19: 8)
    - Fowler, Ruth (Box-folder 19: 9)
    - Japanese – Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 19: 10-13)
    - Koreans - Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 19: 14)
    - Digital copy of Box 20
    - Labor – United States (Box-folder 20: 1-2)
    - Mexicans - Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 20: 3-5)
    - Orientals - Pacific Coast (U.S.) (Box-folder 20: 6-7)
    - Pacific Coast (U.S.) – Emigration and immigration (Box-folder 20: 8-15)
    - Segregated housing – United States (Box-folder 20: 16)
    - Segregation – United States (Box-folder 20: 17)
    - Digital copy of Box 21
    - Segregation – United States (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - Tables and statistical data (Box-folder 21: 2)
    Includes some correspondence.
  - Work plans (Box-folder 21: 3-4)
  - Writings
    - General
      - Unidentified (Box-folder 21: 5)
        Includes fragments.
      - A-Y (Box-folder 21: 6-7)
    - Digital copy of Box 22
    - Gleason, George, "A North-American Race Relations Survey"; "The Pacific Coast Race Survey or a Pacific Coast Contribution to Race Relations,", undated (Box-folder 22: 1)
      Typescript
    - McClatchy, V. S.
      - "The Germany of Asia," Sacramento Bee, undated (Box-folder 22: 2)
        Printed copy
      - Japan's "Peaceful Penetration," Sacramento Bee, 1919 (Box-folder 22: 3)
      - "California's Threatened Hegira of Japanese," Overland Monthly, 1924 (Box-folder 22: 4)
      - "Los Japoneses en California," Overland Monthly, 1924 March (Box-folder 22: 5)
    - Mears, Eliot G.
      - "How Orientals Earn a Living,", undated (Box-folder 22: 6)
      - "Modern Turkey,", undated (Box-folder 22: 7)
      - "Oriental Workers in America,", undated (Box-folder 22: 8)
      - "Will a Low Standard of Living Result in More Production and Force Out Those With a Higher Standard of Living?,", undated (Box-folder 22: 9)
      - "Aids to Teaching International Trade," Educational Review, 1924 October (Box-folder 22: 10)
      - "California's Attitude Towards the Oriental," Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, 1925 (Box-folder 22: 11)
        Typescript and printed copy
      - "The Survey of Race Relations," Stanford Illustrated Review, 1925 (Box-folder 22: 12)
      - "The Younger Generation," Japanese American News, 1926 (Box-folder 22: 13)
      - Resident Orientals on the American Pacific Coast: Their Legal and Economic Status, 1928
        - Typescript (Box-folder 22: 14-18)
          Includes general introduction, outline, and drafts.
        - Digital copy of Box 23
        - Typescript (Box-folder 23: 1-10)
        - Revisions, 1927 June (Box-folder 23: 11)
    - Park, Robert E.
      - "Naturalization,", undated (Box-folder 23: 12)
        Typescript and related materials
      - "A Race Relations Survey: Suggestions for a Study of Oriental Population of the Pacific Coast," Journal of Applied Sociology, 1924 March-April (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 23: 14)
- Photographs, undated (Box-folder 23: 15)
  Two photographs of an unidentified exhibit on Japan.
- Major Documents, 1905-1926 (Boxes 24-32)
  Biographical sketches of participants, case studies, conversation transcripts, extracts from newspaper articles, correspondence, dissertations, essays, interviews, notes, papers, questionnaires, and statements, arranged numerically by document number.
  - Digital copy of Box 24
  - Interview with Lew Shong Kow, ex-President of the Chinese Reform Association, 1924 January 30 (Box-folder 24: 1)
    5 pages; British Columbia
  - Conversation with waiter, International Chop Suey, 1924 February 9 (Box-folder 24: 2)
    1 page; British Columbia
  - Interview: Lambert Sung, interpreter, 1924 February 4 (Box-folder 24: 3)
    4 pages; British Columbia
  - Interview with Reverend D. A. Smith, Superintendent of Presbyterian missions, 1924 February 4 (Box-folder 24: 4)
    7 pages; British Columbia
  - Interview with Dr. Y. P. Lew, Dentist and President of the Chinese Benevolent Association; interpreter, Seto More, agent of the Canadian Pacific Bureau, Ocean Travel, 1924 February 4 (Box-folder 24: 5)
    2 pages; British Columbia
  - Interview with Lum Hing, translator for the Chinese Times, 1924 February 12 (Box-folder 24: 6)
    3 pages; British Columbia
  - Interview with Moore Whaun, advertising manager of the Canada Morning News, 1924 February 13 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Conversation at dinner, Herbert Wang, assistant to Chinese consul, 1924 February 16 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Interview, Herbert Wang, 1924 February 22 (Box-folder 24: 9)
  - Interview, Ko Wing Kan, interpreter and Ginseng merchant, 1924 February 26 (Box-folder 24: 10)
  - Interview with Yip Quong, the first white woman in Vancouver married to a Chinese man, 1924 February 26 (Box-folder 24: 11)
    6 pages; British Columbia
  - Life-history, Herbert Wang, assistant to Chinese consul, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1924 February 28 (Box-folder 24: 12)
    10 pages; British Columbia
  - Visit, home of Ko Wing Kan, 1924 February 20 (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Interview with Miss Coleman, who teaches class of Chinese boys at the Strathcona School, 1924 March (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Luncheon, Herbert Wang, Dr. Park, Miss Raushenbush, 1924 March 6 (Box-folder 24: 15)